Me and my shadow, we take a photo where the horizon meets the sky.
我和我的影子，在天地相接的地方留下一张合照。
My fallen angel, wearing my wet clothes, breathing the scent of you inside.
我坠落的天使，穿着我湿透的衣裳，呼吸着你的气息。
Turn in the light up, squeezing a waterfall from the corner of
把灯光调亮，从角落处拧出一挂瀑布
water from the corner of
从角落的水里
I saw the light from the corner of my eye.
我看见光从我眼角闪过。
Me and my shadow, we are in danger. We don't know how to live with die.
我和我的影子，身处险境。我们不知道该如何与死亡共存。
My fallen angel, why do you want me?
我坠落的天使，你为何想要我？
Why do you come to me at night?
你为何在夜晚来到我身边？
Deep in my bedroom,tell me my mission that comes from up above.
在我卧室深处，告诉我那来自上方的使命。
Guardian from up above.
来自上方的守护者。
I need you to fuck up my whole life.
我要你把我的整个人生都搞砸。
Me and my shadow, we take a photo.
我和我的影子，留下一张合照。
Where the horizon meets the sky.
在天地相接的地方。
My fallen angel, wearing my wet clothes, breathing the scent of you inside.
我坠落的天使，穿着我湿透的衣裳，呼吸着你的气息。
Turn in the light up, squeezing a waterfall from the corner of
把灯光调亮，从角落处拧出一挂瀑布
water from the corner of
从角落的水里
I saw the light from the corner of my eye.
我看见光从我眼角闪过。
Me and my shadow, we are in danger. We don't know how to live with die.
我和我的影子，身处险境。我们不知道该如何与死亡共存。
My fallen angel, why do you want me? Why do you come to me at night?
我坠落的天使，你为何想要我？你为何在夜晚来到我身边？
Deep in my bedroom,tell me my mission that comes from up above.
在我卧室深处，告诉我那来自上方的使命。
Guardian from up above.
来自上方的守护者。
I need you to fuck up my whole life.
我要你把我的整个人生都搞砸。